Employee	Positions
Ankita Anilkumar Chaudhari	QA Engineer
Chetan Krishna Sonawane	Sr. QA Engineer
Chitra Omprakash Srivastava	Sr. QA Engineer
Darpana Kishan Mistry	Sr. QA Engineer
Darshak Rasikbhai Paladiya	Trainee QA Engineer
Gargi Jugalkumar Patel	Trainee QA Engineer
Gaurang Navinbhai Rana	Principal QA
Hetal Ranjitkumar Parekh	Sr. QA Engineer
Jay Bhupendrabhai Patel	Sr. QA Engineer
Jeet Narendrabhai Gajera	Trainee QA Engineer
Kaushik Harishbhai Patel	Trainee QA Engineer
Kavita Suresh Patel	Trainee QA Engineer
Khushboo Herik Mali	Trainee QA Engineer
Kuldeep Kishor Singh	Sr. QA Engineer
Nayan Dilip Akojwar	QA Engineer
Nisha Pradeep Singh	Sr. QA Engineer
Palak Pranav Patel	QA Engineer
Parth Bharatbhai Patil	Trainee QA Engineer
Ranjana Balchanbhai Sonavane	QA Engineer
Sejal Karankumar Patel	Trainee QA Engineer
Viraj Rameshchandra Surati	Trainee QA Engineer
